Southern New England Telephone Company Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series X: Audio/Visual, undated, 1951-1998
  - Reel to Reel Audio Tapes, (5 inch)
    - Commercials (Box 361)
      - SNET
        - Convenience (Rev3) Huff-n-puff (Rev6), undated
        - Decotel, 1972
        - Decotel Phone, 1972
        - Decotel (2), 1973
        - Decotel Extension Phones, 1972
        - Decotel and Selling Brands, 1973
        - Decotel and Extension Convenience (2), 1973
        - Decotel and Trimline (2), 1974
        - Deco Trimline and Cuddlephone, 1974
        - Designline, 1976
        - Doctor and Smart Talk, undated
        - Extension Phone (2), 1971
        - Extension Phone-Girl, 1973
        - Extension Phone-Girl (2), 1974
        - Fall Campaign- Extension, 1973
        - Footsteps, Slow Down and Thanks (2), 1976
        - Get Together by Long Distance (2), 1976
        - Gift General Radio, 1979
        - Gift General Radio, undated
        - Home Improvement Phones (2), 1977
        - Keep In Touch (2), 1977
        - Keep Mottos and Vaudeville (3), 1974 (Box 362)
        - Long Distance Calling-Mother's Day, undated
        - Lovers (2), 1977
        - Mother's Day (5), 1973-1978
        - Mother's Day-Be Choosey, 1978
        - Music Phones and Christmas Voices, 1974
        - News About Long Distance Rates, undated
        - New Extension Spot, 1973
        - Ooh's and Ahh's of Christmas, 1977
        - SNET (4 cuts), undated
        - Soul Decotel (2), 1973
        - Styles and Colors, 1973
        - Sunday and Various Topics, 1975
        - Typewriter and Business Trip, 1976
        - Vacationers (2), 1977
        - Vignettes and Referee (2), 1976
        - Visitors, Right Time and Price Conscious, 1976
        - What City Please? (2), 1976
        - What City Please? (2), 1977
        - Who Do You Know? (2), 1977
        - Who Do You Know? Rates, undated
        - Window Washer, undated
        - WOAS (World on a String) Extension, 1971
        - WOAS Extension, 1971 (Box 363)
        - WOAS Extension (2), 1972
        - Written Number and Long Distance, 1975
        - You Made My Day (2), 1977
        - $10.3 Call (2), 1977
        - “48 for 89cents”, 1978
        - “48 for 89cents” (2), undated
    - Topics (Box 364)
      - Centennial and Long Distance, 1975
      - Centennial Material, 1976
      - Thomas A. Watson, 1976
      - 40th Anniversary of dialogue on film, undated
  - Reel to Reel Audio Tapes, (7 inch)
    - Burchard and Hyde RSVP (WELI Radio Talk Show) (3), 1976 (Box 365)
    - Governor John Dempsey RSVP (3), 1972
    - Van Sinderen, A.W.
      - Competition, 1974
      - Press Conference, 1976
      - RSVP (5), 1972
      - RSVP (2), 1973
      - Speech, New Haven Rotary Club, 1976
  - Record Albums (33 1/3 RPM)
    - Commercials (SNET) (Box 366)
      - Additional Telephones, undated
      - Be A Friend, 1957
      - Call Me, undated
      - Call Out of Town By Number, 1951
      - Christmas Promotion, 1955
      - Direct Distance Dialing, undated
      - Extension
        - Three Blind Mice, undated
        - Sportscaster, Cellar, Upstairs (2), undated
      - Handy Phone (2), 1960
      - It's A Snap, 1965
      - Long Distance (2), 1961
      - Long Distance (2), 1962
      - Long Distance (2), 1963
      - Long Distance, Fall, 1963
      - Princess Telephone (2), 1960
      - Yellow Pages Campaign, 1961
    - Concert and Weekly Bell Telephone Spot, 1956
    - The Importance of Telephone People, undated
  - Video VHS (Box 367)
    - Black and White Footage of Old Telephones, undated
    - Corporate Advertisement “You Know SNET”, 1989
    - Corporate ID “We Are SNET”, 1991
    - From Rhetoric to Action Program
      - Connecticut Officials, undated
      - Governor Roy Romer of Colorado, undated
      - Mary Hatwood Futrell, undated
    - “Going Beyond the Call” A History of SNET (2), 1998
    - I-SNET Connecticut's Information Superhighway (2), 1994
    - Management Tool Kit and Standards of Conduct, 1997
    - Restoring Service “Teamwork and Technology” (Hurricane Bob), 1991
    - SNET Info Minutes, undated
    - SNET Through the Years: “We did a lot together!”, 1995 (Box 368)
    - Still the Oldest and Still the Best: SBC SNET 125th Anniversary Commemorative, 2003
    - “Vietnam: A Chance To Understand” short version (2), undated
    - “Vietnam: A Chance To Understand” long version (2), undated
  - Beta, (1 inch)
    - ATT Newsbreak, 1983 February (Box 369)
    - Concert Celebration Martin Luther King Jr., undated
    - “Happy Faces” SNET TV Show, undated
    - The Past is Prologue Centennial, 1972 March
    - SNET 1980 In Review, 1981 April
    - Stamford Classic Road Race, 1986 April
    - St. Gaudiens, undated
    - The New SNET, 1993 May; note: BETACAM Metal Tape
  - Beta, (3/4 inch)
    - Against The Wind Tornado Restoration, 1989 July (Box 370)
    - ATT Annual Meeting, 1976
    - Business Spots SNET, 1987
    - Corporate Advertising and the GHO, 1986 July
    - CPTV SNET Historic, 1989 March
    - Connecticut's 350th Anniversary, 1986 April
    - The Dream Lives On Concert Promo, 1986 February
    - Field Footage Meriden, 1986 December
    - GHO and Channel 3 SNET Portable Phone, 1986 (Box 371)
    - Introducing the Business Division, 1981 February
    - Lightnet Press Conference, 1983 August
    - Marathon Classic Stamford, CT, 1986 April
    - New Sonecor Network Business Commercials, 1985 June
    - ODC Management Intro, Values, 1987
    - OLIN HQ Fire, 1981, 1988
    - Reach Out for Health Intro, 1983 March
    - Recycling, 1990 September (Box 372)
    - Sonecor Sees the Future, 1986 March
    - Teacher Recognition, undated
    - Video Clips: TV Media and Advertising, 1986 January
    - Window Dubs
      - 1-3, 1983 January
      - 4-6, 1983 January
      - 6-9, 1983 January
      - 9-12, 1983 January
      - 13-15, 1983 January
  - 16 Millimeter Sound On Film, (3 inch reels)
    - Commercials
      - Altone Phone, undated (Box 373)
      - Animated Dial (2), undated
      - Astro (2), undated
      - Automation Industries (3), 1975 October
      - Baby (2), 1969 November
      - Bakery (2), 1974 May
      - Baseball (2), undated
      - Basement (2), [1966?] (Box 374)
      - Bedroom (2), 1966
      - Bell System, The, 1978
      - Business Commercials, 1980
      - Business Phone (2), 1974 April
      - Business Phone “Emergency”, undated
      - Business Telephone (5), 1973
      - Business Telephone (2), undated (Box 375)
      - Car (2), 1974 March
      - Categories (8), undated, 1966
      - Chinese Restaurant (2), undated
      - Chinese Restaurant (2), undated (Box 376)
      - Chocolates (2), undated
      - Chocolates and China (2), undated
      - Christmas, undated
      - Christmas Elf (2), 1974 November
      - Christmas Gift Phones (5), undated, 1964 November
      - Christmas Teenager, undated (Box 377)
      - Confederate General (2), undated
      - Contest (2), [1968?], undated
      - Convenience (2), 1973 April
      - Decotel (4), 1973 April, undated
      - Decotel Christmas (2), 1972 December
      - Deco-Tel, 1972 September
      - Deco-Tel, 1972 September (Box 378)
      - Decotel Phones, 1972 September
      - Decorator Telephone (2), undated
      - Do It Yourself (3), 1973 April
      - Egg Timer (2), 1975 February
      - Extension Phones, 1976 March
      - Energy and Energy Building, undated
      - Family (3), 1976 February
      - Farewell (2), undated (Box 379)
      - Faucet, 1976 March
      - Football (4), undated
      - Gangster (4), undated
      - Gambler (2), undated
      - Gift Certificate, undated
      - Gift Ideas (2), 1974 November (Box 380)
      - Home Phone Decorating (12), undated
      - Home Phone Decorating (2), undated (Box 381)
      - I Like That (4), 1975 December
      - Installer (4), 1971 July
      - J Monday's Child, 1969 January
      - Joe College (3), 1971 July
      - Joe College, undated (Box 382)
      - Kids (6), undated
      - Kitchen (3), [1966?]
      - Laundry, undated
      - Living Book (2), undated
      - Living Room, [1966?]
      - Locksmith (4), undated (Box 383)
      - Martian, 1967 June
      - Mickey, 1979 May
      - Mother's Day (4), 1973 May
      - Motorcycle (4), undated, 1966 January
      - Motorcycle (2), 1965 (Box 384)
      - My Sister The Doctor, undated
      - Niagara (4), undated
      - Operator (6), 1971 July
      - Party, undated
      - Party (3), undated (Box 385)
      - Patches, 1978
      - Pepper (2), [1968?]
      - Popcorn Eaters (3), undated
      - Porch and Patio (2), 1975 August
      - Phone Ranger (3), undated
      - Phone Ranger, undated (Box 386)
      - Phone Store, 1968 February
      - Pitchman, [1968?]
      - Racer (2), undated
      - Rain (2), undated
      - Santa (2), 1970 November
      - Santa Claus, 1968
      - Santa Claus/Phone Store, undated
      - Santa's Workshop, Teenage Times, Trimline Phone, 1974
      - Santa's Workshop, 1968 November
      - Schuster Express, undated
      - Schuster Express, 1974 (Box 387)
      - Sculptures, 1979 May
      - Simple Act (5), 1975 July
      - Simply Beautiful, undated
      - Singing Lineman, undated
      - Skateboard (5), undated, 1965 October
      - Sleigh Ride (2), 1971 November (Box 388)
      - Sports Store (2), 1973 January
      - Squares (2), 1973 April
      - Strike (SNET) (5), undated
      - Styles and Colors (2), undated
      - Styles and Colors (5), 1973-1974 (Box 389)
      - Swimmer (2), undated
      - Teenager (5), 1966 December
      - Telephone Products (2), 1972 February
      - Tree (2), undated (Box 390)
      - Tree-Candlestick (2), 1976 December
      - Trimline (7), 1967, 1974
      - Truck Repair, undated
      - Vignettes, undated
      - Window, 1974 May
      - Window, 1974 March (Box 391)
      - Window Washer, 1977 May
      - Workshop and Tree, 1975
      - World On A String, 1972 March
      - Worn Out, undated
      - Yellow Pages, 1968 August
      - Yellow Pages
        - Bakery, 1974 March
        - Business, 1965
        - Chocolate, [1968?]
        - Kids (2), undated
        - Locksmith, undated
        - Pants, Dog, Glasses, 1977 August
        - Waterbury Welding, 1965 (Box 392)
      - 411 Information, 1968 December
      - 113A Data Phone, undated
      - 1936 Musical (3), 1970 February
      - 1940 Army (3), [1970?]
  - 16 millimeter sound on film, (5 inch reels)
    - Commercials
      - Long Distance, 1971 (Box 393)
      - New Extensions, [1960s?]
      - The World On A String, undated
      - We Hear You, undated
      - Yellow Pages
        - Square, Ignition, Window, Bakery, Sports Store, 1974
  - Microfilm 35 millimeter (arranged by SNET reel #)
    [gaps-dates = when microfilmed]
    - Executive/Financial Department
      - Memorandum of Instrument (Box 394)
        - P0055, 1951 October
        - P0056, 1951 October
        - P0057, 1951 October
        - P0058, 1951 October
        - P0059, 1951 November
        - P0060, 1951 November
        - P0061, 1951 November
        - P0062, 1951 November (Box 395)
      - Contracts
        - P0063, 1951 November
        - P0064, 1951 November
        - P0065, 1951 November
        - P0066, 1951 November
      - Deeds
        - P0067, 1951 November
        - P0068, 1951 November
      - Minutes P0069, 1951 August (Box 396)
      - Financial P0072, 1952 August
      - General Cash Book P0073, 1952 September
      - Financial P0074, 1953 May
      - Memo of Instrument P0075, 1953 May
      - Financial P0076, 1953 August
      - Memo of Instrument P0077, 1953 August
      - Notes P0078, 1954 February (Box 397)
      - Card Record (Woodbury) P0079, 1954 April
      - Stock Shares P0080, 1954 December
      - Financial P0081, 1955 April
      - Financial P0082, 1955 July
      - Bonds P0083, 1956 July
      - Memo of Instrument P0084, 1956 July
      - Financial P0085, 1957 May (Box 398)
      - Contracts, Minutes P0086, 1957 May
      - Bonds P0087, 1957 May
      - Bank Register P0122, 1959 April
      - Stockholder Minutes P0123, 1959 April
      - Company Contracts P0125, 1959 April
      - Bonds P0131, 1961 November
      - Memo of Instrument P0132, 1961 November (Box 399)
      - Memo of Instrument P0135, 1961 January
      - Financial P0136, 1962 October
      - Financial P0137, 1963 March
      - Leases and Deeds P0138, 1963 March
      - Deeds P0139, 1963 March
      - Deeds P0140, 1963 March
      - Deeds, Contracts P0141, 1963 April (Box 400)
      - Contracts P00142, 1963 April
      - Minutes P0143, 1963 April
  - Microfilm 16 millimeter
    - Executive/Financial Department
      - Minutes P0025, 1966 January
      - Contracts P0046, 1967 March
      - Engineering, Grants P0048, 1967 April
      - Accounting P0060, 1968 October
      - Warrant Usage
        - 0063, 1968 October
        - 0064, 1968 October
        - 0065, 1968 October
        - 0066, 1968 October
      - Active Contracts 0071, 1951 November (Box 401)
      - Warrant Usage 0073, 1968 November
      - Budgets 0078, 1970
      - Bonds, Memo of Instrument P0144, 1963 December
      - Memo of Instrument P0145, 1963 December
      - Stockholder Record Card P0149, 1964 April
      - Contracts P0226, 1969 September
      - Accounting, Minutes P0231, 1969
      - Contracts, Leases P0244, 1969-1970
      - Vital Records P0281, 1973 June
      - Vital Records, Contracts, State Projects P0306-307, 1974 June
      - Vital Records P0307-312, 1974 June
      - Vital Records, Minutes P0313, undated
      - Vital Records P0354 (1 of 2), 1974-1975
      - P0354 (2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 402)
      - Contracts P0427, 1970-1976
      - Projects, Contracts, Minutes P0431 (1 of 3), 1975-1976
      - P0431 (2 of 3), 1975-1976
      - P0431 (3 of 3), 1975-1976
      - Debenture List P0434 (1 of 3), 1976 June
      - P0434 (2 of 3), 1976 June
      - P0434 (3 of 3), 1976 June
      - Com Key Equipment Contracts P0449 (1 of 2), 1975-1976
      - P0449 (2 of 2), 1976-1983
      - Minutes P0452, 1970-1972
      - Com Key Equipment Contracts P7700 (1 of 2), 1976-1977
      - P7700 (2 of 2), 1976-1977
      - Contracts, Leases, Deeds P7751 (1 of 2), 1976-1977
      - P7751 (2 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 403)
      - Minutes P7752, 1976-1977
      - Com Key Contracts P7761, 1977
      - Com Key Contracts P7801, 1978
      - Contracts, Leases, Deeds, Legal Minutes P7816 (1 of 2), 1977-1978
      - P7816 (2 of 2), 1977-1978
      - Com Key Contracts P7824, 1978
      - Contracts, Leases, Deeds P7825, 1978
      - Com Key Contracts P7902, 1979 January - July
      - Contracts, Leases, Deeds P7903, 1979 January - July
      - Contracts, Agreements P7940, 1974-1979
      - Com Key Contracts P7954, 1979 August - December
      - Contracts, Leases, Deeds P7955, 1979-1980 January
      - Minutes P8029, 1978-1980
- Series XI: Photographs undated, 1878-1998
  - Contemporary (Box 404)
    - Advertisements
    - Annual Report, 1982
    - Annual Meeting (SNET), 1987 May
    - Audio/Visual
    - Awards (2)
    - Bell Boy Pager
    - Bell Labs
    - Black Management Association
    - Board of Directors
    - Building Engineers
    - Buildings
      - City/Town Halls
      - non-Connecticut
      - non-SNET (2)
    - Buildings SNET (Box 405)
      - Ansonia/Derby, 1948-1965
      - Baltic-Bridgeport
      - Bristol, Brookfield
      - Canaan-Collinsville
      - Columbia-Danbury
      - Danielson-East Hampton
      - East Haven-Fairfield
      - Farmington-Guilford
      - Hartford (2) (Box 406)
      - Hamden-Lyme
      - Madison-Meriden
      - Middlebury-Moodus
      - Moosup-New Britian
      - New Canaan-Newington
      - New Haven (6) (Box 407)
      - New Haven (Box 408)
        - Church Street
        - George Street
        - Orange and Wall Streets (2)
      - New Milford-North Madison
      - Norwalk-Norwich
      - Old Greenwich-Rockville (Box 408)
      - Saybrook-Southington (Box 409)
      - Stafford Springs-Suffield
      - Thomaston-Uncasville
      - Wallingford-Watertown
      - Westbrook-Woodbury
    - Buildings SNET
      - Cafeterias (2)
      - Cafeterias, New Haven, Orange and Wall Streets (Box 410)
      - Central Offices
        - Branford-Guilford
        - Hampton-Norwich
        - Old Greenwich-Winsted
      - Conference Rooms, New Haven
      - Interiors, Lounges, Rest Rooms, 1940s-1950s
      - Interiors, Waterbury
      - Garages
      - Medical Rooms (Box 411)
      - Microwave Stations
      - Repeater and Power Stations
      - Service Centers
    - Buildings State Capitol
    - Bulletin
      - 1975 January
      - 1975 March - April
      - 1975 March - April
      - 1975 August - November
      - 1975 Oct- November
      - 1975 December (2) (Box 412)
      - General Photographs
        - 1975
        - 1976 Summer
        - 1977 (3)
    - Bulletin 1978 January
    - Bulletin 1978 General Photographs
    - Campaigns, Miss Princess, 1960 (Box 413)
    - Career Counseling
    - Carpooling
    - CCTV (closed circuit television) Telecast, Management Info, 1982 December
    - Celebrations, New Haven Symphony Orchestra/Centennial, 1993 May
    - Celebrities
    - Cellular Mobile Service, 1983
    - Check Presentations
    - Children
    - Christmas
    - Churches
    - Commuters
    - Communications Caravan (2)
    - Community Service (Box 414)
    - Company ID Card, 1973 August
    - Computers
    - Computer Data Systems
    - Connecticut Communications
    - Connecticut Scenic
      - Aerials
      - Aerials Bristol and Waterbury
      - Aerials Bridgeport/Fairfield
      - Aerials University of Connecticut
      - Boats Darien, 1956
      - Boats and Bridges (3)
      - Buildings non-SNET (3) (Box 415)
      - Cities/Towns (2)
        - Danbury
        - Darien/New Canaan
        - Hartford
        - Mystic
        - New Haven
        - Ocean Beach New London
        - Rockville
        - Willimantic
        - Windsor Locks
        - Winsted
      - Country Scenes (4) (Box 416)
      - Country Scenes Housatonic River/New Milford/East Haddam
      - Flowers
      - Lakes, Rivers and Waterfalls (2)
      - Monuments/Statues (Box 417)
      - Parks (3)
      - Rural Holiday Hill Cheshire
      - Shorelines
      - Snow Scenes
      - Street Scenes (4) (Box 418)
      - Tobacco Farming
      - Trolley Museum, 1953 August
    - Construction (3)
    - Contests (Box 419)
    - Customer Convenience Products
    - Dimension 2000
    - Directories (new)
    - Data Center
    - Disasters
      - Blizzard, 1984 March
      - Explosion Willimantic, 1971 March
      - Fire, 1956-1974
      - Flood East Hartford to Glastonbury, 1933 April
      - Flood (6), 1936 March
      - Flood, 1936 March (Box 420)
      - Flood Hartford, 1936 March
      - Flood
        - Ansonia, 1955 August
        - Avon/Collinsville, 1955 August
        - Bristol (2), 1955 August
        - Danbury, 1955 August
        - Derby, 1955 August
        - Farmington, 1955 August
        - Hartford, 1955 August
        - Naugatuck, 1955 August
        - New Haven Headquarters, 1955 August
        - [New London?], 1955 August
        - New Milford, 1955 August (Box 421)
        - Norfolk, 1955 August
        - Norwalk, 1955 August
        - Plainville, 1955 August
        - Putnam (2), 1955 August
        - Seymore, 1955 August
        - Simsbury, 1955 August
        - Thomaston, 1955 August
        - Torrington, 1955 August
        - Union City, 1955 August
        - Washington Depot, 1955 August
        - Waterbury, 1955 August
        - Western Electric, West Haven, 1955 August (Box 422)
        - Winsted (2), 1955 August
        - Woodville, 1955 August
        - General Pictures, 1955 August
      - Flood, 1955 October
      - Flood Norwalk, 1955 October
      - Hurricane (4), 1938 September
      - Hurricane (3), 1938 September (Box 423)
      - Hurricane Willimantic, 1938 September
      - Hurricane, 1944 September
      - Hurricane, 1954 May 10
      - Hurricane Carol, 1954 September 1
      - Hurricane Edna, 1954 September 11
        - Clinton-Saybrook, 1954 September 11
        - Mystic, 1954 September 11
        - New London, 1954 September 11
      - Hurricane Hazel Danbury, 1954 October 16
      - Hurricane Donna, 1960 September (Box 424)
      - Hurricane Esther, 1961 September
      - Hurricane Belle, 1976 August
      - Hurricane Gloria (2), 1985 September
      - Hurricane Bob, 1991 August
      - Storms (Ice), 1933 March
      - Storms, 1934 February
      - Storms, 1950 November
      - Storms Madison, 1953 November
      - Storms, 1955 October
      - Storms, 1963 August
      - Storms, 1973 September, December
      - Storms, 1979 September
      - Storms unidentified, undated
      - Tornado Waterbury, 1962 May
      - Tornado Windsor Locks, 1979 October
      - Tornado, 1989 July
      - Tornado Bantam Area, 1989 July
      - Tornado Waterbury/Watertown, 1989 July
      - Tropical Storm Doria, 1971 August
    - Displays Creative Resources, 1983-1987
    - Displays and Exhibits (4) (Box 425)
    - Ecology (3)
    - Ecology (Box 426)
    - Electric Van
    - Electronic Blackboard
    - Emblems and Plaques
    - Emergency Reporting
    - Employee Activities (civic)
    - Employee Activities Hobbies - Sewing
    - Employee Activities (sports)
    - Employee Energy Savers
    - Employment Opportunities
    - Equipment
    - Equipment (911)
    - ESS
    - Exhibits
    - Fairs
    - Fiberoptic Cable
    - Film Bureau
    - Forms
    - Fuel Cells
    - Garages
    - Gift Certificates
    - Ground Breaking (Data Center)
    - Groups, 1960s-1970s (Box 427)
    - Groups Training Classes, 1980s-1990s
    - Handicapped
    - Handicapped Children
    - Infoscreen
    - Japanese Business People
    - Junk Yards
    - Lasers
    - Lightnet Press Conference, 1983
    - Lite-wave
    - Locator
    - Logo (New)
    - Magnetic Bubbles
    - Mail Service Centers
    - Manholes
    - Maps
    - Mechanics
    - Meetings Annual Stockholders, 1984
    - Meetings (2)
    - Memorials
    - Microfilm
    - Microwave Antennas (Box 428)
    - Military (Vietnam)
    - Military, 1952
    - Minority Vendors
    - Mobile Phone Center Van
    - Motor Vehicles
    - Movies (2)
    - Movies “Beyond All Barriers”
    - Movies “The Extra Step”
    - Murals
    - Museums
    - Non-traditional Jobs
    - Office Machines
    - Offices
    - Offices Business Office
    - Open Houses
    - Operator Information (2) (Box 429)
    - Operators (3)
    - Operators (Male)
    - Operators (ZED)
    - Operators (TSPS)
    - Oscilloscope
    - Parking Lots SNET
    - Personalities
    - Personnel (Box 430)
      - Executives and Directors
        - Adams, Dr. Frederick G.
        - Andrews, William F.
        - Ballentine, H.P.
        - Barnes, Fuller F.
        - Barry, J.J. Jr.
        - Basserman, Peter
        - Bennett, Carl
        - Berger, D. Spencer
        - Berger, George W.
        - Beer, R.F.
        - Bennetto, F.
        - Brooks, Allerton F.
        - Buccy K.A.
        - Brunetti, A.J.
        - Bullard, E.C.
        - Caruso, Sue Ann
        - Chittenden, E.A.
        - Clark, D. F.
        - Coe, John A. Jr.
        - Clark, T.E.
        - Cline, Joe
        - Copeland, George G.
        - Cottrell, C.L.
        - Cox B.J. Jr.
        - Curtin, Dave
        - Curtin, J.B.
        - Curtis, Harry B.
        - DeMatteo, Madelyn
        - Denenberg, C.G.
        - DeWitt, J. Doyle
        - Diefenderfer, William E.
        - Directors Group Pictures
        - Divakaruni, Shastri
        - Donofrio, R.M.
        - Doolittle J. Edison
        - Downey, W.D.
        - Drucker, R.S.
        - Etherington, Edwin D.
        - Evans, D.W.
        - Fitzgerald, E.
        - Flether, R.A.
        - Flores-Harper, M.
        - Freese, Carl G.
        - Gatison, B.
        - Gaudiani, Claire (Dr.)
        - Goodspeed, Norwick R.
        - Goodwin, J.E.
        - Graham, Anthony H.
        - Green, H.L.